♠ kangeuge90in eugene-kang90

SUMMARY

Passionate and eager budding developer looking forward to growing in a fast-paced technological landscape. Construction experience building elevator storage units and laboratory experience have helped bolster an aptitude to learn quickly and take on challenging tasks with a purposeful, realistic approach. User experience design focused on optimizing ease-of-use to accommodate people of all computer literacy levels.

EDUCATION

Grand Circus Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

- GPA: 4.0
- After hours Full stack JavaScript Bootcamp

Wayne State University

Aug 2015 - Jan 2017

- GPA: 3.3
- Completed coursework in biology.

SKILLS

Languages: CSS, HTML, JavaScript, MongoDB, Postman, Python, SQL, TypeScript

Tools and Frameworks: Express.js, git, Jest, React

Concepts: Accessible Design, Agile, Pair coding, Test driven development

PROJECTS

Bottom of the Barrel Cocktail Search Application

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

- Developed a cocktail searching single page application with co-student at Grand Circus Bootcamp.
- Employed test-driven development to ensure functionality of application.
- Focus on clean, sleek design with satisfying feedback.
- Utilized firebase cloud, APIs, MongoDB, React, 3D objects, TypeScript.
- https://final-project-eugene-sam.web.app/

ReciMe Recipe Search Application

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- Pair coded a recipe searching single page application with co-student.
- Design focus on simplicity and ease of use for all computer literacy levels.
- Utilized API database, React, TypeScript, Jest.
- https://kangeuge90.github.io/dec4ReactProject2/

Card Matching Game

Aug 2021 - Sept 2021

- Pair coded a timed card matching game with co-student.
- Allowed me to practice test-driven development using dynamic game states and victory conditions.
- Utilized HTML, CSS, 3D objects, JavaScript.
- https://kangeuge90.github.io/Javascript_Project_1/

EXPERIENCE

DoorDash Feb 2017 - Present

• Delivery of food and grocery to customers in a timely manner.

JayWorks Construction

Jun 2019 - Jul 2020

- Traveled nationwide constructing and wiring Modula storage units.
- Worked in fastpaced industrial environments with weekly deadlines.
- Operated in accordance to site/state regulations and safety protocols.

Wayne State University

Mar 2016 - Jan 2017

- Conducted research of Sacchyromyces Cerevisiae in laboratory setting.
- Maintained laboratory and sample conditions in accordance with sanitary requirements.